gurufocus.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy of GuruFocus.com

| 

**** **PRIVACY POLICY**  
Your privacy is very important to us at GuruFocus.com LLC , and we have established and implemented information handling practices for www.GuruFocus.com that we believe are consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organizations doing business on the Internet. This privacy policy describes the practices that apply to our site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information. We have prepared a detailed privacy policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make an informed decision about the extent of your use of our site. 

**When You Visit The Site**  
You can always visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information. When you visit our site we do collect usage information, but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use this data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors , and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to the site. We use this information to improve our site content and ease of use. 

If you register with us, we will have your email address. We will send you periodical email newsletters, from which you can opt out. If you subscribe to our update notification, you will receive emails when we have an update. You can always opt out of these emails. We will never share your email addresses with any other individuals or organizations. If you become a Premium Member we will have your detailed personal information. We will keep this information confidential. If you subscribe our premium membership through PayPal, your credit card is saved at PayPal, which is compliant with the security requirements of all credit card companies. If you pay us directly through the website, the connection is secured. We do not store your credit information on our server. Your credit card information is stored at an off-site location that is compliant with the security requirements of all credit card companies. 

**When You Submit Feedback**  
If you choose to submit feedback to our database , the collection form requires a valid email address. We will not disclose your email address to a third party. We may contact you via email to clarify the information you have submitted. 

**Cookies and Pixels Tags**  
We, or a third-party advertiser acting on our behalf, may place a "cookie" or "pixel tag" on your personal computer when you come to the site or visit a site on which we advertise. These devices are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. We use these devices to collect data to help us personalize and improve your experiences on our site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, your ability to use some features on our site may be impaired. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
We have third-party advertisers on our site. Third-party advertisers may use cookies and pixel tags to gather information about the ads you have seen and the types of things in which you appear interested. These advertisers may use combined information about your visits to our site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services in which you may be interested. This privacy policy does not cover the policies or practices of these third-party advertisers. 

Modifications of this Privacy Policy   
GuruFocus.com LLC reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices in this privacy policy. 

Contact Us   
If you have questions about this privacy policy, please [ contact us](http://www.gurufocus.com/contact.htm) at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

|
